&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以之前，我们描述了，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So earlier, we described, and
我提到了一个叫做抽象操作的东西。
I mentioned a thing called an abstract operation.
如果你还记得，我给你看了两个号码，然后
If you recall, I showed you the two number, and
我说那是个抽象的操作。
I said that's an abstract operation.
所以让我们来谈谈这些是什么，因为它们是基础建筑
So let's talk about what those are, because they are the fundamental building
块，它组成了我们处理类型转换的方式。
block that makes up how we deal with type conversion.
所以你可以在规范中看到，我们有这些抽象的操作来执行，
So you see here in the spec that we have these abstract operations which perform,
从根本上讲，类型转换的任务。
fundamentally, the task of type conversion.
在JavaScript中，我们将类型转换称为强制。
In JavaScript, we refer to type conversion as coercion.
好吗？
Okay?
所以当你想到转换和胁迫时，你真的应该想到它们
So when you think of conversion and coercion, you should really think of them
作为可互换性，至少就JavaScript而言。
as interchangeable, at least as far as JavaScript is concerned.
我们拥有的第一个抽象操作称为ToPrimitive。
The first abstract operation that we have is called ToPrimitive.
显然，如果我们没有原始物，
Now obviously, if we don't have a primitive,
我们需要把它变成原始物。
we need to turn it into a primitive.
所以如果我们有一些非原语的东西，比如其中一种对象类型，比如
So if we have something non-primitive, like one of the object types, like
一个对象，一个数组，一个函数，无论什么，我们需要把它变成一个原语，
an object, an array, a function, whatever, and we need to make it into a primitive,
这是将要涉及到的抽象操作。
this is the abstract operation that's going to be involved in doing that.
顺便说一下，抽象操作不是JavaScript引擎的东西，
By the way, the abstract operations are not a thing the JavaScript engine,
它们不像一个可以通过某种方式调用的函数。
they're not like a function that could somehow be called.
实际上，JavaScript引擎中可能有实际的方法，或者
There may, in fact, be actual methods inside of a JavaScript engine or
不，他们不像被要求是真实的东西。
not, they're not like required to be actual things.
但当我们称它们为抽象时，我们的意思是它们是一个概念性的操作。
But when we call them abstract, we mean they're a conceptual operation.
所以任何时候你有一些东西不是原始物，它需要变成
So any time you have something that is not a primitive and it needs to become
从概念上讲，我们需要做的就是这组算法步骤，以及
a primitive, conceptually, what we need to do is this set of algorithmic steps, and
这叫做ToPrimitive，就好像它是一个可以被调用的函数，好吗？
that's called ToPrimitive, as if it were a function that could be invoked, okay?
因此，ToPrimitive抽象操作接受一个可选的类型提示。
So the ToPrimitive abstract operation takes an optional type hint.
所以换句话说，它说，如果你有不是原始的东西，
So in other words, it says, if you have something that is not a primitive,
告诉我你认为你会喜欢什么，你希望它是什么样的类型。
tell me what you think you would like, what kind of type you would like it to be.
如果你在做数值运算
If you're doing a numeric operation and
它调用ToPrimitive，猜猜它将发送什么提示？
it invokes ToPrimitive, guess what hint it's gonna send in?
它会说，我想要一个号码。
It's gonna say, I would like to have a number.
顺便说一下，这并不能保证你能得到一个数字。
That doesn't guarantee you a number, by the way.
只是暗示一下，我使用它的地方，
It's just a hint to say, the place that I'm using it,
我希望它是一个数字。
I would like it to be a number.
如果你正在做一些基于字符串的事情，猜猜它会发出什么提示。
If you're doing something string-based, guess what hint it's going to send in.
它将发送字符串。
It's going to send in string.
这基本上是唯一的两个提示。
Those are basically the only two hints.
它可以说，我希望它是一个数字，我希望它是一个字符串，或者
It can say, I would like it to be a number, I would like it to be a string, or
我不会告诉你的，所以只要你能给我任何原始的东西。
I'm not going to tell you at all, so just give me whatever primitive you can.
好吗？你需要了解的另一件事
Okay? Another thing you need to understand about
JavaScript中的算法是它们固有的递归，
the algorithms within JavaScript is that they are inherently recursive,
这意味着他们定义了一些东西，例如ToPrimitive。
which means that they define something, for example to ToPrimitive.
如果从ToPrimitive返回的结果不是一个原语，如果它是另一个
If the return result from ToPrimitive is not a primitive, if it's another
非原始的，就像另一个物体，然后它会再次被唤起，并且
non-primitive, like another object, then it's gonna get evoked again, and
它会一直被调用直到我们能得到一些
it's gonna keep getting invoked until we can get something that's
一个实际的原语，或者在某些情况下得到一个错误，好吗？
an actual primitive, or in some cases get an error, okay?
所以有很多这样的规范阴谋发生
So there's a lot of these sort of spec machinations that happen
它们是递归的。
that are recursive.
当我们稍后研究强制平等时，你会看到这个想法，它是
And when we look at coercive equality a bit later, you'll see this idea that it's
一次又一次的重复应用直到我们得到一个完整的结果。
sort of being re-applied over and over and over again until we get a full result.
所以到Primitive，它的工作方式，本质上，就是沸腾的算法。
So ToPrimitive, the way it works, essentially, boiling down the algorithm.
它的工作方式是有两种方法可以
The way it works is that there are two methods that can be
在任何非基本体上可用。
available on any non-primitive.
任何对象，函数，数组，任何东西。
Any object, function, array, whatever.
任何非原语，都有这两个函数。
Any non-primitive, there are these two functions.
你几乎可以肯定以前见过这些。
And you've almost certainly seen these before.
valueOf函数()和toString()函数。
The valueOf function() and the toString() function.
这个算法说，如果你告诉我提示是数字，那么我会
And this algorithm says, if you've told me that the hint is number, then I'm going
首先尝试调用valueof()，如果它在那里，然后看看它给了我什么。
to first try to invoke the valueOf(), if it's there, and see what it gives me.
如果它给了我一个原语，那么我们就完了。
And if it gives me a primitive, then we're done.
如果它没有给我一个原语，或者它不存在，那么我们尝试toString()。
If it doesn't give me a primitive, or it doesn't exist, then we try the toString().
我们要么得到一个原始的，要么没有。
And we either get a primitive or not.
如果我们两个都试了，而且
And if we tried both of those, and
我们没有得到一个原语，通常这最终会导致一个错误，好吗？
we don't get a primitive, generally that's gonna end up resulting in an error, okay?
如果暗示是数字的话。
That's if the hint was number.
如果提示是字符串，他们只需颠倒查询的顺序，
If the hint was string, they just reverse the order that they consult them in,
但他们基本上还是会咨询这两个人。
but they still essentially consult both of them.
因此，如果提示是字符串，我们将请求该对象，即非原语，
So if the hint is string, we would ask for that object, that non-primitives,
toString()方法，如果有，请使用它返回的内容。
toString() method, and if it has it, use what it returns.
如果它合法地给我们一个像字符串一样的原语，
And if it gives us legitimately a primitive like a string,
它应该是这样的，那么我们就用它。
which it should, then we'll just use that.
然后我们会尝试value of()，好吗？
And then we'll try to valueOf(), okay?
所以请记住，如果你要使用不是原语的东西
So just keep in mind, if you're gonna use something that is not a primitive in
一些肯定需要原语的地方，比如数学或连接。
some place that definitely needs primitives, like math or concatenation.
在你的脑海里，你应该意识到，
In your mind, you should realize,
它最终将通过这个ToPrimitive算法来强制它，并且
it is going to end up coercing it through this ToPrimitive algorithm, and
它最终将调用valueOf()或toString()。
it's gonna end up either invoking the valueOf() or the toString().
稍后我们将看到这些用法的示例。
We'll see examples of the usage of those in a little bit.